<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text 2</string>
    <string name="article_title">Insider Trading Allegations Rock OpenSea, NFT Marketplace
        Responds</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle"><b> Chastain, OpenSea’s head of product, is at the center
        of the scandal that emerged on Twitter on Tuesday night.</b></string>
    <string name="article_text">In a statement issued Wednesday morning, leading non-fungible token
        (NFT) marketplace OpenSea said it uncovered evidence of insider trading by one of its
        employees.
        \“Yesterday we learned that one of our employees purchased items that they knew
        were set to display on our front page before they appeared there publicly,\” the statement
        reads.
        \n\n
        The statement doesn\’t have a byline, but the public relations team for Andreessen
        Horowitz, a major investor in OpenSea, has been handling company communications around
        the scandal, which comes less than two months after OpenSea snagged a $1.5 billion
        valuation in a $100 million funding round.
        \n\n
        In a thread, the Twitter user assembled a paper
        trail of transaction receipts tied to Nate Chastain, OpenSea\’s head of product. Chastain,
        the Twitter account alleged, was investing in NFTs just before OpenSea featured them on
        the front page of its website, and then cashing out on the consequent price increase.
        \n\n
        Chastain didn\’t immediately return a request for comment.
        \n\n
        Insider trading on NFTs is, of
        course, not explicitly illegal yet, because there\’s so little legal precedent for digital
        assets on the blockchain, but OpenSea is coming down hard anyway.
        \n\n
        The company says it\’s
        implementing new policies that prohibit this kind of behavior.
        \n\n
        \“For a new, more open
        internet that empowers creators and collectors, we will need to bake in trust and
        transparency into all that we do,\” reads the statement. \“We/’re committed to doing the
        right thing for our users and earning back the trust of the community we serve.\”
        \n\n
        Click this link for more crypto news www.coindesk.com/business/
        \n\n</string>
    <string name="add_comment">Add Comment</string>
</resources>